Guide to the Walter Thabit papers, 1950-2004
Thabit, Walter papers, 1950-2004
- Series VI. Studies
  - Surveys (SF)
    - SF-26: Manhattan Valley Surveys (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - SF-27: East Flatbush Structural Survey (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - SF-28: Poughkeepsie - Gate St. Cost Ests. (Box 44, Folder 35)
      Rehabilitation Evaluation from Poughkeepsie Project
    - SF-29: Poughkeepsie - Union St. Surveys (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - SF-30: Poughkeepsie Surveys - Jefferson St (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - SF-31: Jersey City (Box 44, Folder 38)
      Citizen participation survey
    - SF-32: Hoboken Survey Forms (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - SF-33: East New York Structural & Other Surveys (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - SF-34: Survey Forms, Var. (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - SF-35: Union Street Rehab. (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - SF-36: Structural Surveys - Residential (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Information Maps, Mylars and Other Studies (Oversize)
  - Freeport, Long Island Studies, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Mylars and prints
  - Community Activism Posters, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Cooper Square, Park Slope (Methodist Hospital), Rockefeller, eviction
  - East Flastbush, Brooklyn, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Mylars and prints of information maps and design studies
  - East Midtown (CB#6), undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Mylars and prints, information maps, photographs (most of the Mylars for this project are in Map Case Folder 5)
  - "Planning for the Target Area, East New York" poster materials, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
    Mylars, prints, photographs and mock up
  - Poughkeepsie: Union Street images, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    2 prints
  - Poughkeepsie - Union Street/Downtown Project, 1969-1971 (Map-case Folder 1)
    Information Maps, Surveys, Mylars
  - Hoboken and Newark, 1966-1972 (Map-case Folder 2)
    Hoboken Model Neighborhood, Maps, Plan for Shalom Towers
  - Cooper Square Rehabilitation Project/Lower East Side, 1961-1978 (Map-case Folder 3-4)
    Information Maps, Mylars, Housing Plans. Some community activism posters
  - Manhattan: Various Locations, 1967, 1970s, undated (Map-case Folder 5)
    Morningside Heights/Upper West Side Project(near Columbia University) - Mylars and Information Maps; East Midtown - Mylars, maps; Map of Manhattan neighborhoods and potential projects.
  - East Flatbush, Brooklyn, undated (Map-case Folder 6)
    Information Maps, Mylars
  - Brooklyn: Various Locations, 1968, undated (Map-case Folder 7)
    Brownsville - Information Maps; Red Hook/Columbia Heights - Information map; Map of Brooklyn and potential projects
  - East New York, Brooklyn, 1961-1968, undated, 1997 (Map-case Folder 7-9)
    Information Maps, Mylars, and prints from the 1960s (Folders 7-8) and a second study in the 1990s (Folder 9). Community activism poster.
  - Freeport, Long Island, 1975, undated (Map-case Folder 10)
    Information Maps, Mylars, prints
  - Hartford; Philadelphia; and misc. projects, 1960-1972, undated (Map-case Folder 11)
    Also includes a shipping map of the Ports of New York; White Lake, NY Quadrangle Map; Oklahoma City and Vicinity Map; unlabelled plans (near a Golf Course)